I often think of the person I have a
long spiel I do I'm not going to do it
okay I'm going to save you the trouble
but I think about the guy who invented
uh farming right and they were
hunter-gatherers before that they went
out in the forest they tried to find
some wild berries they tried to find
rice
sometimes they did sometimes they didn't
when they didn't find her eyes for
enough days the family died and that was
the way it was you wandered around the
forest and if you got lucky you lived
for another week you see what I mean
that was the old way what do we do now
take some seeds
dig in the ground put the seats there
and cover it with technique
fertilize it properly correct watering
not too much not too little
all at the same correct time know the
technique of farming and you will have
rice next year that's how
and because of the invention of farming
it's civilizations can rise people have
time to read books and write books and
write music and Jazz and
and and have a city you can't have a
city
of gatherers hunter-gatherers cannot
make cities okay in our stage of
evolution in this world
everybody in this world almost everybody
is a hunter-gatherer
they are wandering around Phoenix
looking for money you know hoping to
find some you know or a partner or a
yoga class that can make them young you
see people are wandering around Phoenix
looking hoping you know and and
according to it
a really
a Diamond Cutter State of Mind these
people are all crazy they're all like
cavemen
they are just like cavemen and then
there's they're stunned a person say
what what'd you do today I went looking
for a job
why I need money
why didn't you just plant some
I don't know how you see we are like
that you see
imagine if I know how suppose I know how
to plant money imagine how frustrating
it is to watch people suffer their whole
life looking for money out in the forest
and if they don't get it they die right
so here's how you've planted just learn
to plant it
and I truly believe that it will change
the future of
of our world I believe it's another step
in Civilization I believe that 50 years
from now if our work succeeds
people will just plant what they need
where
tell me where
in other people okay this system is like
an echo
or a basketball okay you can't make an
echo without a war
you cannot bounce at basketball without
a flaw you cannot plant a mental seed
without another person who is in need
it's not possible cannot be done okay so
the first job in this system is I have
to find someone who wants some money
you see it sounds crazy right I want to
make money what are you going to do well
of course I have to find someone who
wants money and then help them make
money